Produced by Kadokawa Daiei Nippon TV Dentsu S.D.P.
Kadokawa-Daiei Studio presents .
Produced by KUROI Kazuo .
Planning . Original by AKIMOTO Yasushi .
Script by TAIRA Minako .
Chakushin Ari You 've Got A Call One Missed Call .
Tsutsumi Shinichi as YAMASHITA Hiroshi Caretaker .
Fukiishi Kazue as KONISHI Natsumi .
Nagata Anna as OKAZAKI Yoko .
" After you have finished recording your message , press ♪ . "
" You will be connected to a Customer Service Representative who will handle ... "
Kishitani goro as OKA Caretaker Tsutsui Mariko as MIZUNUMA Mari .
Ishibashi Renji as MOTOMIYA Detective .
Directed by MIIKE Takashi .
Izakaya Japanese Pub .
Yes , Gladly . Hai , Yorokonde ~ !
I 'm telling the truth !
No way !
It 's true !
She 's afraid of a peep-hole .
She can 't peep through the hole .
Why ?
Why ? It beats me .
Yumi-chan .
Yumi-chan !
Why are you " Peep-Hole Phobia ? "
That 's not it .
Natusmi is making up stories .
No , I 'm not .
In the physical exam ,
she could not take the " Eye Test " .
Just because she feels ...
something scary inside the hole .
Sounds like a trauma .
In man 's memory
the most difficult one to forget is
" fear " , they say .
Is that so ...
There is a friend of mine ...
who lives in an apartment
whose previous tenant committed suicide .
He once told me ...
in the bathroom ,
when he was washing his hair ,
he felt something behind him .
Bringing up goose bumps .
When he tried to look back ,
On his shoulder ,
he saw a very abnormally thin ...
woman 's hand ...
Woowahhh ...
Yoko !
What happened to you ?
My junior friend of mine at high school died .
Say ...
eh ?
April 16 21 : 44 PM .
Why did she die ?
While scuba diving ,
she got lost from her friends
and ended up drowning .
April 16 ( Wed ) 21 : 44 PM .
Death by suffocation is
excruciating painful , they say .
When her body was recovered ,
her face showed gruesome pain .
Yoko , a phone call .
Eh ?
That 's not my Chaku-Melody Ringing Tones .
But it 's Yoko 's phone that is ringing .
From whom ?
No name . Just phone numbers .
What ? !
Chakushin Ari You 've got a call .
What is this ?
What 's up ?
This is my Cell phone number .
Huh ?
Playing the " Recorded Message 1417 " 21 : 45 PM .
There is one recorded message in your Inbox .
The latest messages ... # 1
18th ...
eh ? !
Evening ...
11 : 04 PM
The message is ...
Oh no ! Iyada !
It 's started raining . Ame Futte Kichatta .
Oh , no ! Iyada !
Isn 't this voice ...
There is no way that you get a call
from your own Cell phone .
Then , what is it ?
Besides " 18th " means
the day after tomorrow .
It 's Yoko 's voice , isn 't it ?
How on earth is it possible !
Do you know what you are saying ?
Aah ! It must be a prank joke
from your boyfriend .
If I had a boyfriend ,
I wouldn 't come to Gokon party . ( singles party )
If you 're really single and free ,
why not go to Kawaguchiko Lake ?
A friend of mine owns a hotel pension there .
Sounds great !
I 'm on !
I 'll organize everything .
Give me your Cell phone numbers .
Sure thing . OK ...
Pass this to Yumi-chan .
Eh ?
Yumi-chan 's number .
Sure .
Police Morgue .
Rina 's corpse .
What are you doing ?
Nothing .
Why are you so anti-social ?
We must keep her body at the Police .
The circumstances strongly suggest homicide now .
Mr. Caretaker ...
Your sister 's name ...
Was that Ritsuko-san , wasn 't it ?
Among the various indications
of the Child Abuse and Neglect ,
There is a case we should discuss .
For example ...
one child hits
other child 's head for small matters ,
Thus , showing wild and violent behavior .
Introductory Child Psychology Nyumon Jido Shinri Gaku
a daily contact with such a child ...
can see that one finds
a much more weaker figure as his target ...
Shunsuke I have another enragement . I must cancel today 's date .
Shunsuke . I have another enragement . I must cancel today 's date .
You are damping Shunsuke now ?
Yes . Kenji is cool , isn 't he ?
My kind of type ...
To other children , small and or weak ones ...
Hey you !
You in " Purple " dress !
What 's the theme of this lecture ?
" Abuse " ... Gyakutai ga ...
creates " Abuse " ... Gyakutai o umu
probably ... Mitaina ...
Mmm ... that 's correct .
For each of the case studies ,
we 'll discuss next week .
I must be going now for my part time work .
See you !
She is so carefree now .
What 's up ?
Nothing ...
Yes ?
Yumi ?
Yes .
Do you want to join me for shopping tomorrow ?
Eh ?
There 's swim suit sale .
Kenji says he likes sea .
I want to pick up a cute one to impress him .
OK
Yoko , where are you right now ?
What ?
I can hardly hear you .
It 's about time we found a new part-time job .
What 's going on ?
Yumi ?
Can you hear me ?
Hello ~ !
Yoko !
That voice message 's time !
18th !
Isn 't that 11 : 04 PM tonight ?
Voice message ?
Sorry , I can 't hear anything .
Eh ? !
What did you say ?
Oh , no !
It 's started raining .
Yoko ...
Aaaaaaaaahhhh !
April 18 23 : 04 PM .
Yoko ! What 's up ? !
Yoko !
What are you doing right here ?
Did you hear ...
that Yoko ...
didn 't die instantly ?
Eh ? !
Her " right arm and leg " was chopped off .
But she was still conscious ...
Out of dying breath ,
she reached for help .
No way ...
I bet ...
she was killed
Yoko Senpai ...
What do you mean by " killed " ?
Tell me what you know , please !
Yoko-senpai did receive a call
from her own Cell phone .
So ?
Death-messaging call !
Death-messaging call ?
Rina received the call .
Rina ? Who is she ?
Is she the one who died from diving ?
After killing Rina .
From Rina 's Cell phone ,
it called Yoko Senpai 's Cell phone .
What do you mean by " killed " ?
You know who killed her ?
I 'm not so sure ...
But I heard it 's a woman
who had left grudges in this life .
Eh ?
Through Cell phones ,
it finds the next victim .
And then ...
It picks a new victim
from the Cell phone 's memory .
And keeps on killing people , as chain call of death .
You had better register
your Cell phone number
as " Never Accept Calls From This Number " Chakushin Kyohi .
Let 's go !
April 21 15 : 28 PM .
Yoko died . 3 days ago ...
in a train accident .
Does it have anything to do
with that prank call ? Itaden ( Itazura Denwa )
Yes .
Same day , same time .
Leaving the same message
as in the recorded ones .
It 's definitely fishy , isn 't it ?
But ...
The cause of her death is suicide .
This isn 't my voice , is it ?
The 1st message is ...
21st ...
15 : 34 PM ...
Shoot ! Yabe ~ !
I totally forgot ... Kanzen wasureteta .
No way ...
Waaaaaaaahhh !
No way !
That sort of thing would never happen !
" 21st " means today !
Only 2 minutes to the appointed hour .
There is no way !
You 're trying to frame me , aren 't you ? !
Aah , it must be ...
Mikamis asked you to do this . Right ?
No , Kenji-kun , that 's not it !
You made it all up , didn 't you ?
It 's a sick joke !
I almost got caught !
Hey ! Kenji !
What ?
Oh , yo !
Don 't " Oh , yo ! " me .
Aren 't you the one who called us
to decide what to show
at a school 's culture festival ?
Shoot !
I totally forgot ...
April 21 15 : 34 PM .
Waaaaaaaahhh !
Is this the right floor ?
What 's up ?
Police Interrogation , alright ...
but it is intended for general reference purposes only .
Kawai Kenji-kun fell down from the elevator shaft by accident .
Even testified by his friend .
That was not it .
I 've already told the other person .
Yoko and Kenji 's Cell phones received ...
Okazaki Yoko-san plunged to her death from a railway bridge into a moving train .
There are witnesses who claim to have seen her jump .
If that 's not suicide ,
what do you call it ?
I don 't know ... but ...
She must have been a drug user .
There is no way .
Everything in life has its challenges and its reasons ...
Any crime can be explained logically .
Beyond common sense , that one unthinkable ,
unmistakable thing is happening right now .
Is that so ?
Thank you for your cooperation .
So what they 'd told us became true .
From Yoko 's Cell phone
to Kenji 's Cell phone ...
It 's true Yoko 's Cell
stored Kenji 's number .
In Kenji 's Cell phone
our phone numbers were stored ...
It 's from a boyfriend from high school days .
Hello ?
Natsumi !
It 's the same Ringing Tone ... as Yoko 's case .
Not mine .
Yumi ...
You 've got a call . ( 1 ) Message .
Why ? I turned off the power source .
April 23rd ...
The day after tomorrow ...
April 23rd ( Wed ) 22 : 39 PM Caller Konishi Natsumi .
Ah ...
Wahhhh !
Noooo !
Hey you guys ! What are you doing ?
I don 't trust these things , but you know ...
I talked with Megumi .
No worry .
It 's just a rumor ...
Keep your chin up .
See you .
Yumi , you should delete your number .
You , too , want to delete your numbers , don 't you ?
I 'm sorry .
I just want to make sure this is supposed to work ...
Delete mine , too .
Me , too !
Mine , too !
Hey !
Yumi !
This is the cancellation form .
Kindly fill in this form .
Yes .
Do you wish to carry back your phone ?
Dispose it , please .
Yes , please .
I understand .
We 'll reset the data inside .
There is nothing to worry about your security .
Roll the film !
Which one is Konishi Natsumi-san ?
Are you Konishi-san ?
You are Konishi Natsumi-san
who has received a death-messaging call .
Please don 't !
We have our resident Psychic Medium .
Do you want us to perform Jyorei , Exorcisms ?
Jyorei ?
I know you 're pressed for time .
22 : 39 PM tomorrow will come shortly .
Natsumi , let 's go . Move away , please .
Wait !
Can I see your Cell phone ?
She had already canceled the contract .
Eh ? !
Is that right ?
Imai !
Yes !
Give me your Cell phone !
Your phone ! Quick !
Hold this !
Hold this .
Shoot the Cell phone first .
Konishi-san !
Is this the Cell phone
that received a death-messaging call ?
What are you saying ? !
Natsumi !
Will you stop it already ? !
What the hell is going on ?
Stop everything .
Konishi-san ...
This is really bad .
The death might really come to you .
You had better talk to the Psychic Medium .
Come with us .
We 'll help you .
You know Tendo-sensei , don 't you ?
Famous for Jyorei , Exorcism .
I 'm sure he will help you .
Let 's go .
We 'll go back to the studio .
Natsumi !
Let her go !
Yumi ...
I 'll go with them .
I don 't want to be like " Yoko and Kenji . "
OK , let 's go .
You go down the stairs and shoot when we are coming out .
Yes .
Let 's go .
I 'm sorry .
Wait !
If you know something , tell me , please .
Unless otherwise , Natsumi is doomed to die !
When was it ?
Appointed time ?
Tomorrow ... 10 : 39 PM .
Isn 't it Yoko 's ...
Why do you have her ...
The time she was hit by a train ?
11 : 04 PM .
One minute later ,
This is the number ,
her Cell phone called .
Outgoing History April 18th 23 : 05 PM Called Number 0352293339 .
What does it mean ? Yoko called ?
Not possible !
Her right hand that grabbed the Cell phone
was chopped off .
And it was found in a different place
where the rest of the body was found .
Then , who called ?
Who the hell called the number ?
April 22nd 15 : 23 PM Called Number 0352293339 .
Oct 17th 16 : 32 PM Called Number 0352293339 .
The same number . Whose number is this ?
You call the number now .
" The number you have dialed is not in use . "
" Please check the number and dial again . "
Whose Cell phone is this ?
It 's my sister 's .
6 months ago ...
She got a call from her own Cell phone .
3 days later , she died from fire .
Jawbreaker ?
Yeah .
Why such a thing ?
No idea .
When my sister was rescued ,
she was still alive .
She was suffering from 10 degree 's burn .
But yet , she was still conscious .
The physician called it a miracle .
But I felt ...
If she can 't make it after all ,
Why not give her a peaceful death ?
Kagami Hospital Kagami Byoin .
This is our old hospital 's phone number
before we relocated here .
For emergency call .
When did you move ?
It was 5 months ago .
Wasn 't she a patient of yours ?
Her name is Okazaki Yoko .
After you called us ,
I checked our records .
There was no record
of her admittance for treatment .
Kusaka-san , a call from Dr. Sato .
Yes .
Sorry , I must be going now .
Phone calls to this hospital ...
What kind of meanings are linked to it ?
Tomorrow ... 22 : 39 PM ...
APRIL 23RD 22 : 39 PM Exclusive Coverage !
You might witness the shocking moment .
Emergency Live Show !
The college girl who received the death-messaging call !
APRIL 23RD 22 : 39 PM Special Emergency Broadcast !
A ringer that connects all mysterious deaths .
Then , a new death-messaging call reached her Cell phone .
What kind of fate is waiting for her ?
APRIL 23RD 22 : 39 PM Life or Death ? !
APRIL 23RD 22 : 39 PM Will she come out alive ?
Can this program save her from her fate ?
APRIL 23RD 22 : 39 PM EXCLUSIVE LIVE COVERAGE !
I 'll go to the studio to meet Natsumi .
This sound ...
Here we go .
Breathe in .
Breathe out .
This sound ...
Just before Kenji fell down to the shaft ,
I heard this sound in an elevator .
Asthma patient 's body ...
I thought you could answer my questions .
Jobs we received from the Kagami hospital
for the past year is ...
Yellow color of the skin .
Entire body is yellowish .
Cirrhosis of the Liver .
Yellow eyeballs ...
He must have suffered a lot .
Look very carefully . His left leg is swollen .
Typical symptom of heart failure .
Far from the heart , organs started to die .
It is a slow death .
Body must suffer .
But there is no worry .
You lose consciousness .
This is not it .
It might be a bit too harsh on you ...
What ?
What 's going on ?
What 's this ?
Mizunuma Mimiko 10 years old 2002 / 09 / 21 Declared death at Kagami Hospital
7 months ago , she died of infantile asthma .
( M ) Matsuda Yoshimi Matsumura Sensei Mizutani Maki Mizunuma Marie Mitsui Kaoru Miyake Masako .
Mizunuma Marie ?
Eh ?
It 's deceased Mimiko-chan 's mother 's name .
Let me use your phone .
Do you know the address of Mizunuma-san ?
Yes , but ...
Nobody lives there .
Eh ?
Fatherless Family and such ...
After funeral ,
this mother ...
abruptly ...
disappeared .
We haven 't been paid for the funeral costs .
Hello ?
Hello .
This is Mizunuma Residence .
We can 't come to the phone right now .
After the beep , please leave your message .
Always the same recorded message even on her cell phone .
I must tell you this .
If you die ,
you 'll be in this database .
Hello ? Natsumi ?
Hey , how have you been ?
Natsumi !
Do you know Mizunuma-san ?
Yeah !
What 's the problem ?
We go on air tomorrow .
Will you check this ?
No . If you don 't know , it 's OK .
Natsumi , you shouldn 't appear on TV .
I 'm telling you that Tendo-Sensei 's time
to be moved up 30 minutes .
Have him check the stage set .
He 's so picky , you know .
Is this Psychic Medium really credible ?
Come on ! There is no way we can do that .
Can you take the responsibility ?
Then , Yumi , you 'd do something instead ?
Natsumi ...
Looks nice .
This wardrobe is a bit too bright .
I must hung up .
Find a bit darker one .
Wait ! Natsumi .
Natsumi !
Here .
My sister 's appointment book .
She worked for the Children 's Guidance Office .
July 18th ...
Mizunuma Mimiko-chan ... Asthma attack
July 21 Mizunuma Nanako-chan swallowed thumb tacks .
That 's Mimiko-chan 's sister .
Mimiko-chan ... Asthma attack
July 26th ... Mizunuma Nanako-chan .
Light burn on her left thigh
July 30th ... Mizunuma Nanako-chan .
Pestiside went into her left eye .
Emergency treatments
at Kagami Hospital ...
9 times !
In July only .
Hello ?
I 'll come to the office tomorrow .
Then ,
I 'll quit .
I was just fired .
Children 's Guidance Office .
Mizunuma Marie had been abusing her daughters .
Probably ...
But we could not come to that conclusion on the committee .
Why ? They came to hospitals so often .
Certainly , Nanako-chan 's sickness and wounds were frequent .
She had never hidden anything .
On every occasion ,
either Marie-san or Mimiko-chan called for help .
Besides , doctors and nurses told us ...
Marie-san was making an exceptional effort
to care for Nanako-chan .
Even without enough sleep .
Munchausen Syndrome By Proxy Dairi Munchausen Shoukougun .
How did you know ? !
Ritsuko-san was suspecting Munchausen syndrome by proxy .
By proxy what ?
Munchausen Syndrome By Proxy Dairi Munchausen Shoukougun .
MSBP is a mental disorder
in which a person falsely reports or causes symptoms
in another healthy person under his or her care .
Why ?
To satisfy one 's crave for attention and the limelight .
In a word ,
a caregiver in this case , a good mother ,
receives attention ,
sympathy ...
and appraisal .
For such a stupid purpose ?
Physically harm her own child to produce symptoms ?
It is often related to the abuser 's childhood experience .
In fact ,
when Mimiko-chan went into convulsion .
There is a rumor
that Marie-san was beside her .
But she ignored her .
Poor Mimiko-chan ...
She was a kind child ,
who took good care of her sister .
Eh ? !
This is very bad .
What ?
Her face was not so visible last time , was it ?
Police does not and will not ...
work on a murder crime
that has not been committed .
Natsumi might be killed today !
Is that so ?
Didn 't I tell you ?
It 's useless .
What ? !
If Police had investigated
my sister 's death 6 months ago properly ,
there wouldn 't be this many victims .
Victims ? Who are you referring to ?
Okazaki Yuko , Kawai Kenji -
I found the same jawbreakers from their mouth .
They are all fucking victims !
Pretending to be a detective is fun ?
Don稚 get carried away .
Do you care for some candies ?
I 'll go to the TV station alone .
Eh ? !
Cancel Cell now .
And don 't get involved .
But Natsumi is in trouble !
If you don 't want to be alone ,
go back to your family .
My family house ...
I 've never been there since high school graduation .
I 'm coming , too .
Hey !
Excuse me ... Pardon me ...
We 'll hold a conference time later .
No worry . Keep your chin up .
Tama-chan ! Are you ready ?
Yes !
I 'll attach a mic here .
Natsumi !
Off limits to outsiders .
Call the guards ! Remove them !
Let 's go !
Yumi ! TV doesn 't do anything good .
One minute to on-air !
Hurry up !
Excuse me ! Pardon me ! Make way , please !
Natsumi ! Natsumi !
One minute to on-air !
We 'll go to Cam ♪ 4 !
Cam ♪ 2 stand by !
Natsumi-san goes into the center stage .
Stand by . Wait for my Cue !
You stand by right here , OK .
First we count 5 and then live on air at 2 .
Hey , hey , you are in the way !
30 Seconds to on-air ! 30 Seconds to on-air !
Great place ... I discovered lately ...
Cheap and Yummy .
Hello ? Kaori-chan ?
I can 't talk to you now .
Hey ! MC ! Respond to me !
Attention ! 10 seconds to on-air !
5 seconds , counting !
Finally the time has come .
What will you do
if you got warnings of impending death
by your own voice
through your own Cell phone ?
Tonight we get together a team
to investigate this death-messaging call ,
that shook our entire country .
We go on live with this Emergency Broadcast
and you see with your own eyes
what this is all about .
One co-ed received this death-messaging call .
The appointed time is tonight ,
on this day , April 23rd .
At 10 : 39 PM .
It is exactly 38 minutes from now .
We brought together Experts in Paranormal Phenomena .
Hirayama Masakazu-san ,
Isobe Akira-san .
Furuki Emika-san .
Give us your hands , please .
Just started !
Aren 't you watching ?
Let me know when the Ghost shows up .
First let 's go to the video tape
to recreate what had happened .
You don 't fit ...
as a detective .
Let 's welcome Konishi Natsumi-san
who had received this dreadful message .
Please come over here .
Follow her move !
Can you talk ?
Please be seated .
I 'll ask you lots of questions that you may or may not be able to immediately answer .
First Konishi-san , I 'll ask you straight out .
I heard that you had lost 2 friends lately .
Is it true ?
Yes .
I see ... it is true .
One thing in common between the two is
each Cell phone shows the
incoming call from his or her own Cell phone .
Recorded Message has a date and time stamped in the future .
On the appointed day and time .
On the appointed day and time , they died . What a beautiful profile !
If it 's a prank , it 'd cost a lot of work .
And this time , Konishi-san 's Cell phone
received this video images
instead of her own voice messages .
The Death Warning Count-down timer processing 25 : 00 .
Run the Video .
I had gone drinking with her several times
I must say that I got surprised .
Rather shocking I should say
within a short period of time ,
two students from the same school died .
The Death Warning Count-down timer processing 19 : 53 .
Possibly a distorted human relationships ...
From psychological point , you might want to say so , but .
This is " Paranormal Phenomena . "
You always talk that way .
Less than 15 minutes to the appointed time .
15 seconds to commercial .
What is going to happen to her ?
After commercial , we 'll welcome Tendo-sensei , our resident Psychic Medium .
Music , Enter !
Will she come out alive from the studio ?
Now we go into commercials .
Good !
So far , so good !
Not good . Not working well .
No , you 're doing OK .
The stage is yours , Tendo Hakusui-Sensei .
We need your help more than ever .
Tendo Hakusui Psychic Medium .
" Nomaku sanmanda bazaradan senda makaroshada sowataya un tarata kanman " .
Homage to the all-pervading Vajras ! O Violent One of great wrath ! Destroy ! un tarata kan man .
FUDO MYO-O , Wrathful King of Mystic Knowledge , to protect his devotees from disaster ,
from harmful or dangerous people , and from spells or other negative magic .
With no categories , this mysterious power saves all beings ; suffering goes , happiness comes .
I knew ...
this incident .
5 years ago , at the end of the year ,
I was suffering a high fever .
At that time , Konishi-san ,
I had already met you .
Under the sunshade parasol
you were crying .
In the purity and clarity of Heaven ...
In the purity and clarity of this world ...
I am ...
alone ...
In the purity and clarity of ...
Did you fix this , Kudo-chan ?
No , I didn 't do anything .
Aaaaaaahh !
No ! Stop there !
No !
Out of my way !
Hey !
I must get in !
Let me in !
Gyaaaaaahh !
CM ! Go to Commercials !
No ! No commercials ! Go on !
Roll it ! OK , Right ? !
OK , Right ? !
Natsumi !
Hwaah !
Natsumi ...
Natsumi !
I 'll take you to the hospital .
Waaaaaaaaaahhhh !
Aaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhh !
Aaahhhhhhhh ...
April 23 22 : 39 PM .
Gwaaaahhhh !
Gggwaaaa ...
Nakamura Yumi .
You have received ( 1 ) new message .
The first message is ...
24th
19 : 13 PM .
Why ? Doushite ?
Nakamura Yumi 's Apartment .
You 'd better take a rest .
Call your friend .
Have him stay with you .
Until then , I 'll be with you .
How about a drink ?
Can I open beer or something ?
Tomorrow ...
It 's useless .
It 's unavoidable , it just happens .
Tomorrow night ...
Just like Natsumi ...
Don 't give up .
16 hours to go ...
What do you think I can do ?
What 's that scar ?
You by any chance ...
Abused by your parents ?
By my mother ...
How about your father ?
He didn 't stop your mother ?
He was seldom at home ...
My Granny had always tried to save me .
Yumi ?
Call Granny here .
Yes !
Granny !
I 'm sorry .
Ouuuuuuu !
Kyaaaaaaaaaaaaahhh !
Hey !
What 's up ?
I 'm sorry .
Are you alright ?
What 's up ?
Hey !
Are you alright ?
I 'm sorry .
Mizunuma Marie 's Apartment .
She had just disappeared
leaving everything behind .
I 'm in trouble .
Return the key on your way back .
Here you are .
You don 't have to take your shoes off .
I 'll have to clean everything anyway .
Mizunuma Marie Mimiko Nanako .
This !
As of November 23rd , 14th year of Heisei , ( 2002 )
we terminate your Cell phone service contract
due to non-payments .
Then , how come we connected
to the Message Service Center ?
Where is the phone connected to ?
Waaaa !
What 's up ? !
Aaaaa ... aaaahhh ...
yeaaaahhh ...
You should go home and take a rest .
I 'll take care of the rest .
Musashino Ikujiin Musashino Orphanage .
Yes , that 's her .
Nanako-chan ...
Nanako-chan , do you know where your mother is ?
Nanako-chan .
Sorry , but ...
She can 't talk .
Eh ?
Not from birth ...
But from abuse , most likely ...
Nanako-chan ...
Your bear is sick again ?
Any words from her mother ?
During these 6 months ...
None at all .
This melody ...
This ?
Some time ago ,
It became popular from one of Children 's TV program .
Where 's your Mom ?
You don 't really know ? !
Sorry .
I 'm sorry .
Do you happen to know where Mizunuma-san is ?
Well ...
At that time , unless she was physically working
she was practically living in the hospital .
She was more knowledgeable about the hospital
than the newly recruited nurses .
Well then ...
What is being built on old hospital site ?
Nothing .
It hasn 't been torn down - yet , I should say .
Eh ?
Yamashita-san , it 's me .
I told you to go home .
I couldn 't sit still .
Old Kagami Hospital is still standing there .
I 'll pay a visit now .
W - Wait ! Wait ... I 'll go .
What 's the address ?
I got it .
You stay in the room .
But !
T ...
Time is pressed .
But I will come to see you .
Do you understand ?
Then , see you .
Thank you very much .
Thank you .
April 24 18 : 49 PM .
Old Kagami Hospital Ruin .
Yamashita-san ...
Yamashita-san .
Yamashita-san ?
Received a call from Nakamura Yumi .
Waaahhhh !
Aaaahhhh !
Waaaaaaahhhhh !
Yeaaaaaaahhhhhhh !
Waaahhhh !
Yumi !
Yumi ! Yumi !
It 's me !
Are you OK ?
Let 's get the hell out of here !
Waaaahhh !
Y
You .
Your .
Your I.
Your li .
Your lif .
You life .
You life will .
You life will be ended .
You life will be ended in .
Your life will be ended in
56 seconds .
55 seconds .
Nooooooooooooo !
Shit !
Yumi !
... Calling ... Nakamura Yumi .
Mizunuma Marie 's Cell phone ?
Come on !
Stop this fucking call !
April 24 19 : 13 PM .
It 's over .
Everything is alright now .
Probably ...
it 's Mizunuma Marie 's corpse .
You 'd better not look .
She wanted to be found by someone ...
Gwaaaaaaaaahh !
Yumi !
Brother !
Ritsuko ...
Brother ...
There are various skies
to every one .
Mother ...
I won 't run away from you .
I 'll be a good girl ...
I 'll stay with you forever .
I 'll stay with you , Mother ... forever here .
I 'll do anything you say .
More than 6 months have passed since she died .
And one more thing .
This phone 's call history contains .
Okazaki Yoko , Konishi Natsumi
and all other victims ' phone numbers .
I contacted Mizunuma Nanako 's orphanage .
The Orphanage Director has something you should take a look at .
Me ?
Will you come to the orphanage with us ?
No worry .
We 'll take good care of Nakamura-san .
Shall we ?
Musashino Orphanage Hope Room .
This ...
I found it in Nanako-chan 's bag .
What is it ?
This is Mizunuma Marie 's room .
To the hospital ...
I 'll take you there .
Sorry , I 'm late ...
I was right ...
Mimiko , you 've been doing this .
The one who has been harming you
was not your Mother
but your sister ...
Tell me ...
But my sister always
popped a jawbreaker into my mouth .
" I hope you 'll recover soon " , she said .
Mom !
I can 't breathe .
The one who 'd killed " Ritsuko and Natsumi "
is not " Marie ! "
It 's Mimiko !
Eh ? !
W ... What do you mean ? !
Probably " Marie " is the first victim .
The deceased Mimiko accessed .
Marie 's Cell phone .
W ... Wait a minute !
Then ...
I 've been trying calling ...
but I can 't connect to Yumi .
Send someone immediately !
Yumi !
Yamashita-san ?
It 's me !
Yumi , are you alright ?
Yamashita-san ?
April 24 19 : 13 PM .
Why ?
Yumi !
Yumi ...
What is the matter ?
Where is Mimiko ?
Huh ?
You are alright .
You 're really alright ? !
I 'm so relieved ...
To the hospital ...
I 'll take you there .
Ikutsuka No Sora by SHIBASAKI Kou Lyrics-Akimoto Yasushi Music Composition-Jin Nakamura Any Skies .
Kono Sora Wa Tatta Hitotsu Dato There was only one sky ...
Itsu Karaka Omotteita Noni I have been thinking this way .
Miageta Kokoro No Muki De By changing the way I look .
Chigau No Wa Naze Darou I 've found a new sky .
Itoshisa Ni Setsunai Hikage Ga If the shadow is casted over my feelings of love .
Doko Mademo Tsuzuiteiru Nara And if it 's a long everlasting one ...
Mirai Ga Mienakutemo Though I don 't know what awaits in the future .
Chizu Ni Nai Ano Kado O Magarou I 'll turn that corner that 's not listed in the map .
Sayonara Sayonara Good bye Good bye .
Anata Ni Aitai I want to see you .
Dokoka De Mou Ichido I want to see you again somewhere .
Sayonara Sayonara Good bye Good bye .
Guuzen No Youni As if it 's a coincidence .
Kodoku No Sono Saki Ni The end of this loneliness .
Atarashii Sora Ga Aru leads to the new sky of tomorrow .
Sayonara Sayonara Good bye Good bye .
Anata To Wakarete After we broke up .
Ichibyou Ato Demo Even a second later .
Sayonara Sayonara Good bye Good bye .
Furi Muite Shimau I can 't help looking back .
Ashiato Wa Tsuzuku Yo Your foot steps continue .
Ikutsuka No Sora No Shita under different skies .
Directed by MIIKE Takashi .
Dust Sub 08-28-2004 for Babel ~ Truenco ~ Melinda ~ BigE ~ Sparky . - - delsxyz ~ Chiyoaki at a. b. m. j .